Guide to the Cornell University News Service records, [ca. 1920s-2000s].
Cornell University News Service records
- Series VI. Cornell University News Services records, 1920s-2000s
  - Subseries VIb. Photographs
    - People
      - Individuals by last name
        - Meloy, Margaret (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 155)
        - Meredith, Dennis L. (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 158)
        - Gordon Messing, 8/22/88; 0037 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Meyer, Elmer, 1970-1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 22)
        - J. William Middendorf (Former Secretary of Navy) (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 13)
        - Miller, Russell (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 157)
        - Miller, Sherry (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 39)
          In Yokohama Japan with family of Tomoko Noda as part of an exchange program.
        - Billy Mills (Gold Medal Winning Athlete) (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 13)
        - Minch, Bradley (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 158)
        - Mingle, James (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 159)
        - Prof. Nariman Mistry in control room, 12/19/88; 0174 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Prof. Nariman Mistry, 12/19/88; 0175 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Mistry, Nariman (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 160)
        - Mohrmann, Helen (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 161)
        - Sonya Monosoff and Joyce Lindorff (w/violins and harpsichord), 10/18/88; 0108 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Statler Hotel: Hans Weishaupt, Dick Moore, David D'Aprix, Caroline Lampiasi, 3/10/89; 0251 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Moran, Richie (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 163)
        - Moran, Richard - Hall of Fame, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 36)
        - Moravic, Phyllis, 1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 37)
        - Delta Kappa Epsilon Tree/Ryozo Morishita, 2/11/89; 0206 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Jay Morley/Fun in the Sun, 9/3/88; 0048 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Morrison, George, 1969-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 38)
        - Motemagno, Carlo (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 162)
        - Daniel Patrick Moynihan (Senator) (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 13)
        - Susan Murphy, Dennis' Birthday, 8/9/88; 0021 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Murray-Rust, Catherine (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 164)
        - Edmund Muskie (Senator) (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 13)
        - Mrs. Fleda Straight Myers (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 39)
        - Vladimir Nabokov (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 23)
        - Ralph Nader (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 13)
        - Nagi, Syed (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 165)
        - Arthur Neal (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 39)
        - Nelson, Suzy (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 166)
        - Nepal Ambassador/Center for Jewish Living, 10/22/88; 0114 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Anil Nerode, 10/11/88; 0098 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Tom Neuhaus at the Mayer School, 11/1/88; 0119 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Tom Neuhaus at the Mayer School, 11/1/88; 0120 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Neuhaus, Thomas (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 167)
        - Neville Parker (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 39)
        - New, Maria (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 168)
        - Newell, Roger (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 40)
        - Newman, Floyd (Class of 1912), 1976-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 41)
        - Newman, Floyd (Class of 1912), 1976-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 42)
        - Newman, Floyd (Class of 1912), 1982-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 43)
        - Newman, H. Michael (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 169)
        - Newton, Mary Ann, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 44)
        - Nigerian Ambassador (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 24)
        - Alan Nixon - new faculty, 9/23/88; 0066 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Professor's Noblitt and Sola, 10/5/88; 0089 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Norton, Eleanor Holmes (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 170)
        - Mr. and Mrs. Jansen Noyes (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 13)
        - Noyes, Nicholas, 1970-1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 47)
        - Nye, Bill (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 1)
        - Robert Louis Oakley (Chimesmaster), 1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 22)
        - Oblak, Janiece (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 171)
        - Sandra Day O'Connor (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 13)
        - Olguin, Ben (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 172)
        - Olin, John and Spencer, 1966-1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 49)
        - O'Neill, Kathleen (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 173)
        - John Opel (Chairman of IBM) (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 14)
        - John Opel (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 23)
        - Opperman, Mary (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 174)
        - John Ostrom and Sandra Carrington, 1/13/89; 0181 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Owings, Nathaniel ('26) with Felix Candela, 1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 50)
        - Owings, Nathaniel, 1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 51)
        - Pai, Dinesh (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 175)
        - David Parker and new chimes practice stunt, 3/3/89; 0240 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - George Pataki, 1997, 1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 15)
        - Pauling, Linus (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 176)
        - Katy Payne and Whale signals, 2/20/89; 0230 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Pearsall, Sam, 1963 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 52)
        - Peckenpaugh, Norm (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 177)
        - Sherman Peer (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 39)
        - Clarence Pendleton (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 14)
        - Charles Percy (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 14)
        - Percy, Charles (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 178)
        - Perez, Pedro (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 179)
        - Perkins, James, 1962-1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 53)
        - Perkins, James, 1963-1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 54)
        - Perkins, James (Contact Sheets), 1966-1967 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 55)
        - Perkins, James - Speaking in the Temple of Zeus, 1968 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 56)
        - Perkins, James (Contact Sheets), 1966-1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 57)
        - Perkins, James - Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 58-59)
        - Perkins, James - Interview, 1963 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 60)
        - James Perkins (photographs) (Box 4-3-15 - 124, Folder 9)
        - Perkins, Mrs. James (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 1)
        - Donald Peterson (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 14)
        - Peterson, Donald (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 180)
        - Pew, Joseph Luncheon, 1968 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 3)
        - Cranch, Edmund T. (Dean of Engineering), with Dana Woroniecki and Carolyn Phillips, V.P. of Society of Women Engineers, 1973 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 52)
        - Phillips, William E. (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 181)
        - Ph. T. "degree", 1958-1959 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 4)
          Dean McConnell, Mrs. Norman Gary, Mrs. Chas. Thomas, group, 1958, 1959
        - T. Boone Pickens (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 14)
        - Jose Piedro - new faculty, 10/5/88; 0087 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Samuel Pierce (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 14)
        - Pinto, Blenda (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 182)
        - Udar Pinto (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 20)
        - Platt, Robert C. (Student Trustee ‘73), 1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 5)
        - Christopher Plummer (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 14)
        - Giok Po Oey and SE Asian Books, 1973 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 6)
        - Helen Prejean (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 26)
        - Price, David (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 183)
        - Protter, Philip (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 184)
        - Purcell, Robert, 1969-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 22)
        - Nathan M. Pusey (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 39)
        - Raffensperger, Edgar M. (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 185)
        - Raffensperger, Shirley (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 186)
        - Raj, Rishi (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 187)
        - Richard Ramin, 8/18/88; 0030 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Ramirez, Jose (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 199)
        - Hunter R. Rawlings Inauguration Press Kit Photographs, 1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 126, Folder 2)
        - Hunter R. Rawlings (Box 4-3-15 - 126, Folder 3)
        - Gordon W. Reed (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 39)
        - Reich, John, Guest theatre director, 1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 23)
        - Richard E. Reynold's Game Farm, 1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 24)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T., 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 25)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T., 1977-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 26)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T., 1977-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 27)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T., 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 28-31)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. with Alumni, 1977-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 32)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. with Family, 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 33)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. and Rosa, 1977-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 34)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T., 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 35-36)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. with Alumni, 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 37)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. at Commencement, 1978-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 38)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T., 1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 39)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T., 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 40)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T., Cornell/China Program, 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 41)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T., 1977-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 42)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T., 1980-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 43)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T., 1980-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 44)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. (Contact Sheets), 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 45)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T., Alone and with Faculty and Staff, 1977-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 46)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. with Alumni, 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 47)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. at Commencement, 1973-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 48)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. at Commencement, 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 49)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. with Kiplinger, 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 50)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. with the Public, 1977-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 51)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. at Sporting Events, 1977-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 52)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. with Students, 1974-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 53)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. with Students, 1981-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 75, Folder 54)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. with Students, 1978-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 1)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. and Rosa, 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 2)
        - Rhodes, Frank H.T. and Rosa, 1979-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 3)
        - President Frank Rhodes with Chinese Delegates (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 14)
        - Rhodes, Fred H., 1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 4-5)
        - Rhodes, Fred H. - Professorship Dinner, 1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 6)
          Celebrating 40th anniversary of establishment of a Chemical Engineering degree at Cornell (The Warehouse in Ithaca)
        - Riker, Bob, Design Engineer, 1973 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 7)
        - Syed S. H. Rizvi & apple storage system, 7/1/88; 0005 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Cholesterol removal: Syed Rizvi, 12/20/88; 0176 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Steve Robertson - new faculty, 9/23/88; 0067 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Jack R. Robinson (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 39)
        - Robison (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 23)
        - Robison, Ellis, 1974-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 8)
        - Governor Nelson Rockefeller with James Perkins (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 27)
        - Rogers, Adele and William, 1970-1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 9)
        - Rolle, La Verne ('74), 1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 10)
        - Guillermo Weber/Jon de Roos - new faculty, 9/26/88; 0072 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Lewis Roscoe, Keith Ickes, 8/4/88; 0014 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Douglas Rosenthal (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 14)
        - Clint Rossiter (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 23)
        - Arthur Rubenstein (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Arthur Rubenstein (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 23)
        - Dean Rusk (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 22)
        - Pierre Salinger (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Salinger, Pierre (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 189)
        - Schassburger, Ron with Wolves, 1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 11)
        - R. Schlesinger (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 39)
        - Jean Way Schoonover (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Jack Scott (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Prof. Russell Barton and Naketo Scott, 1/24/89; 0186 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Prof. Russell Barton and Naketo Scott, 1/24/89; 0187 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Norman Scott, 2/7/89; 0200 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Dr. Robert C. Seamans Jr. (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 39)
        - Seeley, Jason with Sculpture, 1969-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 12)
        - Copied slides: Tom Seeley, 1/9/89; 0179 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Semmelhack, Martin F., Chemistry, 1973 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 13)
        - Seremetis, Stephanie V. (‘72), 1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 15)
        - Constance Shapiro - infertility expert, 11/29/88; 0155 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Sheff, Richard A, 1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 16)
        - Neal Sher, 11/28/88; 0153 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Arkady Shevchenko (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Prince Norodom Sihanouk (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Prince Norodom Sihanouk (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 23)
        - Steven Slack - new faculty, 10/5/88; 0091 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Curtis Sliwa (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Prof. Smidt and Andrew Leong, 11/17/88; 0145 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Janet Sniezek - new faculty, 9/14/88; 0057 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Summer College Student Jennifer Snyder, 8/5/88; 0019 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Lee Snyder, 8/10/88; 0024 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Professor's Noblitt and Sola, 10/5/88; 0089 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Theodore "Ted" Sorensen (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 40)
        - Wole Soyinka (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Spencer, Mrs. Nancy, 1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 18)
        - Bert States (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 40)
        - Roger Staubach (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Gloria Steinem, 1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 18)
        - Stettnek, Adam (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 190)
        - Stevens, Betsy (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 191)
        - Stevens, George (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 192)
        - Stevens, Randy (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 193)
        - Stevenson, Adlai and Sir Eric Ashby (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 20)
        - Lewis A. Stimson (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 40)
        - Stone, Bruce J. (‘74), 1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 76, Folder 21)
        - D.F. Stone (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 23)
        - Stratton (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 20)
        - Strong, LeNorman (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 194)
        - Subramanian, Devika (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 195)
        - Sugarman, Stephen L. (Student Trustee), 1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 78, Folder 14)
        - Suzuki, Yuri (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 196)
        - Swift, Howland (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 197)
        - Sylvester, Jamie S. (‘73), 1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 78, Folder 16)
        - Susan Szasz and compact disc at Olin, 3/3/89; 0239 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Szasz, Susan (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 198)
        - Szelenyi, Szonja (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 199)
        - Tabacchi, Mary (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 200)
        - Taber, David (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 201)
        - Dr. Elkind, Jan Talbot & AIDS pamphlet/Forensics Team, 9/13/88; 0056 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Talbott, Jan (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 202)
        - Prof. Tang's Assistants, Laser research, 6/29/88; 0001 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Tasker, Sarah (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 203)
        - Dame Kiri Te Kanawa (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Thomas, Marney (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 204)
        - Robert Thompson (Assistant Secretary for Agriculture) (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Thompson, Scott (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 205)
        - Thompson, William (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 206)
        - Ron Thwaites (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 40)
        - Tian, Sophie (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 207)
        - Tien, Norman (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 208)
        - Tkachuck, Cynthia (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 209)
        - Topping, Peter (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 210)
        - Father Tormey, 1966 (Box 4-3-15 - 78, Folder 18)
        - Trautman, Charles (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 211)
        - Trefethen, Lloyd (Nick) (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 212)
        - Trudeau, Robert (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 213)
        - Tsai, Harrison (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 214)
        - Dick Warner/Hotel Faculty Reception, 8/29/88; 0043 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Tucker, Warwick (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 215)
        - Tufford, Peter E. (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 216)
        - Peter Tufford, Michael Whalen, 8/3/88; 0013 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Uris, Harold and Ruth, 1972-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 78, Folder 33)
        - Harold Uris (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 23)
        - Vargas-Mendez, Leonardo (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 217)
        - Vaught, Russ (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 218)
        - Vickers, Sarah (ILR), 1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 78, Folder 35)
        - Vietnam Ambassador, 1962 (Box 4-3-15 - 78, Folder 36)
        - Vigneaud, Vincent Du, 1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 78, Folder 37)
        - VIPS - Arlene Alda through Aaron Copeland, 1971-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 1)
        - Voiland, Bonita (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 219)
        - Waldron, Jeremy (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 220)
        - Waller, Robert (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 221)
        - Wang, Jane (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 222)
        - Wang, Shou Eric (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 223)
        - Ware, Barlow (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 224)
        - Vale Warke, 10/10/88; 0095 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Warren, Beth (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 225)
        - Guillermo Weber/Jon de Roos - new faculty, 9/26/88; 0072 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Weber, Guillermo (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 226)
        - Webster, William (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 227)
        - Weeks, Anne (Bookbinder [Contact Sheets]) (Box 4-3-15 - 78, Folder 51)
        - Weinberg, Andrew D. (‘75), tests effects of marijuana on mice, 1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 78, Folder 52)
        - Leonard Weinstein and Tree Chamber, 10/14/88; 0102 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Hans Weishaupt, mgr. Statler Hall, 8/1/88; 0010 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Reception for Hans Weishaupt, 9/1/88; 0047 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Statler Hotel: Hans Weishaupt, Dick Moore, David D'Aprix, Caroline Lampiasi, 3/10/89; 0251 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Statler Hotel: Hans Weishaupt and Neal Geller, 3/15/89; 0258 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Weishaupt, Hans and Neal Geller (Hotel School), 1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 78, Folder 53)
        - Weiss, Stephen (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 228)
        - Weissinger, Tom (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 229)
        - Welch, James (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 230)
        - Wendt, William (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 231)
        - Peter Tufford, Michael Whalen, 8/3/88; 0013 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Cornell Historical Photographs (Ezra Cornell and Andrew Dickson White) (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 30)
        - White, Mrs. Andrew Strong (Claire Howard White / Claire Alcee), 1966 (Box 4-3-15 - 78, Folder 54)
          Viewing portraits of herself and her late husband in President White Library (Uris Library)
        - Will W. White (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 40)
        - Wiesel, Elie (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 232)
        - Wiesenfeld, John R. (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 233)
        - George Will (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Deitrich Willers (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 22)
        - Willford, Andrew (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 234)
        - Dr. Brackette Williams (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 26)
        - Dennis Williams, 3/13/89; 0254 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Robin Williams (Visiting Sociology Professor) (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 17)
        - Malcolm Wilson (Governor) (Box 4-3-15 - 79, Folder 20)
        - Wolf, Ed (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 235)
        - Student Profile: Marty Wolfer, 2/24/89; 0233 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Dr. Alan Wood and Gypsy Moth - Virus, 2/13/89; 0217 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Dr. Alan Wood and virus/Avner Arbel and computers, 2/13/89; 0218 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Wood, Alan (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 236)
        - Cranch, Edmund T. (Dean of Engineering), with Dana Woroniecki and Carolyn Phillips, V.P. of Society of Women Engineers, 1973 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 52)
        - Irving S. Wright (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 40)
        - David Wyatt and Thai Inscription, 3/13/89; 0255 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Memorial Room/Zhang Xinxin, 12/14/88; 0171 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Xinxin, Zhang (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 237)
        - Yarrow, Peter (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 238)
        - Christian C. Yegen (Box 4-3-15 - 132, Folder 40)
        - Alison Casarett, David Yeh, 8/4/88; 0015 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - David Lewis/Dr. Yen - new faculty, 10/10/88; 0096 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
        - Yoder, Olen (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 239)
        - Younger, Irving and Judith, 1974-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 78, Folder 55)
        - Zelnick, Bob (Box 4-3-15 - 98, Folder 240)
    - Events
      - Ackerman Rally, April 17, 1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 1)
      - AIDS Awareness, 1990-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 2)
      - Alumni Council Meeting, 1956-1962 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 3)
      - Alumni Council Meeting, 1960 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 4)
      - Alumni Honors and Awards, 1975-1983, 1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 5)
        Includes College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Outstanding Alumni Award winners, 1989: Wendell Earle, Edwin Slusarczyk, Robert Greig, Gilbert Levine, Joseph Peck, 1990: Herbert Kling. Also John H. Laragh winner of the Alumni Award of Distinction 1993.
      - Alumni VIP Phone-athon, 1973-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 6)
      - ANC Conference, 11/19/88; 0147 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Anything that Floats, but a Boat Race, 1971-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 7)
      - Arbor Day, 1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 8-9)
      - Art Department and Art Exhibitions, 1959-1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 10)
        Prof. Norman Daly
        Prof. James Mahoney
        Student art exhibition 1962
        Various artist
        Fuertes paintings
        Thackeray drawings
        Kramer collection, 1960's and 1970's
      - Art: USA (Exhibition at the Johnson Museum), 1967 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 11)
      - Awards, 1996-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 12)
      - Berrigan Weekend, Barton Hall, "Spontaneous Sound," "Black Panther", April 17-19, 1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 13)
      - Black Gospel Festival, 1991-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 14)
      - Book Awards, 1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 15)
      - a: Booksale/Chimes, 11/2/88; 0121 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Business School Activities and Events, 1975-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 16)
      - Business School Executive Summer Session (Contact Sheets), 1967-1973 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 17)
      - C.A.C.O. (Cornell Association of Class Officers), 1969-1970, 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 18)
      - Campus Activities, 1982-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 19)
      - Campus Community Activities, 1971-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 20)
      - Campus Sales, 1969-1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 21)
      - Campus Sales, 1970-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 22)
      - Campus Sales, 1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 23)
        March 1969 - Small items sale at Willard Straight
        1970 - Plant sale
      - Campus Sales - Jordani Club, Small animal sale, 1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 24)
      - Campus - Pots and Pan Sale, 1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 25)
      - Campus - Willard Straight Hall, 1971-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 26)
      - Centennial Convocation, 1964 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 27-29)
      - Centennial Convocation (Contact Sheets), 1964 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 30-32)
      - Centennial Exhibit, 1965 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 33)
      - Centennial in NY, 1965 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 34)
      - Ceremonies, 1961-1967 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 35)
      - Charter Week (Contact Sheets) (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 36)
      - Chicago Conference, 1967-1968 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 37)
        1967 (Pick-Congress Hotel)-George Kahin, David Mozingo, John Lewis, Steve Muller
        1968 (Sheraton - Blackstone)
      - Commencement, 1936-1957 (Box 4-3-15 - 80, Folder 38)